You see, remember, the slope is
equal to the thermal expansion
coefficient--
thermal expansion coefficient.
And those slopes are the same
for the different glasses.
Just because I've
cooled one differently,
they're not going to
have different slopes.
And this is the
fundamental challenge.
This is the fundamental
confusion point
that happens which is
that this is not time.
This axis is not time.
So this is wrong to.
What we're doing is we're
talking about something
involving time, cooling rate.
But we're plotting
it on something
that doesn't involve time, and
that can lead to confusion.
So I wanted to point that out.
You say, well,
shouldn't the slope
be different because you're
cooling it slower or faster?
No, that's not
what this slope is.
This slope is a thermal
expansion coefficient.
So the right answer
to this must be
that you have your
nice liquid phase
and you've made
your two glasses.
So here's one.
This has cooled faster.
This is slower.
This would be Tg.
This would be another
Tg, maybe Tg1, Tg2.
And the Tm would
come down and have--
well, I've run out
of room here, but Tm
might come down like this.
And so T1 must be
somewhere up here.